(Sheldon:)It's an outrage. Honestly, I'm
tempted to leave the university.
(Howard:)You know, if you're
really serious about that,
(Howard:)I hear there are some
exciting opportunities
(Howard:)in home care for the old and fat.
(Leonard:)Whatever you do,
just don't make any rash decisions.
(Sheldon:)I don't know. I am really aggravated.
(Raj:)When I'm feeling low,
I have sex with a girl.
(Raj:)But that's just me.
(Howard:)-Oh, come on, give her a chance.
-No.
(Nurse:)No, life, it is too short.
(Bernadette:)I know you've only been here
a day and a half,
but you're like part of the family!
(Bernadette:)I don't think the service
is gonna send any more people.
(Howard:)Yeah, maybe it's time we just
release Ma back into the sea.
(Bernadette:)That's not helpful.
(Howard:)Well, then, we may need
to get used to the idea